piratedrive.com 2016-04-06

# Privacy Policy - Asia Travel & Leisure

##  [ Privacy Policy](https://asiatravelandleisure.com/privacy-policy.html)

**Asia Travel & Leisure** respects your privacy and we will do our utmost to ensure the information you supply is kept private and secure. We protect the privacy of your personal information. This applies to information supplied to us in the following situations:  
    * Making an enquiry  
    * Requesting a brochure  
    * Making a booking  
    * In a tour registration form  
    * Subscribing to our newsletter  
    * Entering a competition  
    * Under any other agreement or arrangement  
 **How is your personal information used?**  
The information you give helps us provide you with personalised service. When you supply information about yourself for specific purposes, we use the information for that purpose only (i.e. to provide the service or information you have requested). If making a booking with us, additional information will be required for operational reasons.  
We do not share, sell or rent information to any third parties. Asia Travel & Leisure is anti-spam. If you receive information from Asia Travel & Leisure, it is because you have asked to hear from us, you have entered a competition and agreed to join our mailing list, or a friend/colleague has requested it on your behalf.  
 **Choice to opt out**  
If you have registered to receive communications from us and later change your mind, you may contact us to have your name removed from our distributions lists. Our e-newsletter gives you the option to unsubscribe via a link at the bottom of the page. Alternatively, you can contact us via email.  
 **Who views your information?**  
Asia Travel & Leisure may disclose personal information to other members within the company where necessary to fulfill our purposes.  
We may also disclose your personal information to third parties (contractors to whom we contract out certain services) for the purpose for which the information was collected.  
For example, we currently engage third party contractors to:  
    * Provide transport, including flights  
    * Organize and operate tours  
    * Provide software and hardware application hosting services  
In these situations we prohibit the third party contractor from using personal information about you except for the specific purpose for which we supply it.  
Other than the above we will not disclose your personal information without your consent unless disclosure is either necessary to prevent a threat to life or health, authorised or required by law, reasonably necessary to enforce the law or necessary to investigate a suspected unlawful activity.  
 **Transfer of information overseas**  
We may transfer to people in foreign countries any of your personal information to fulfill the purposes set out in this Privacy Statement (e.g. international offices of Asia Travel & Leisure, airlines, hotels, tour operators and ground handlers).  
In the majority of cases the transfer of the information will be necessary for the fulfillment of our obligations.  
 **Anonymous information collected**  
In order to ensure our websites are relevant and appropriate to the majority of users, anonymous click-stream information is collected from every visitor. This includes pages viewed, date and time and browser type. IP numbers are used to determine domain type and in some cases, geographic region. We do not make any association between this information and a visitor’s identity.  
 **Site cookies**  
Asia Travel & Leisure uses cookies as you visit pages on our websites to facilitate some functions such as making a booking or entering a competition. Cookies contain anonymous information only and are never used to retrieve any information about your identity.  
 **Links**  
This site may contain links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links you are entering another site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.  
 **Sensitive information**  
We only collect sensitive information about you with consent.  
 **More information**  
If you have any questions, concerns or comments, please email [care@asiatravelandleisure.com](mailto:care@asiatravelandleisure.com)
